

wangivy1108@gmail.com

User Experience & Interface Designer

https://ivywang1108.github.io/ivyportfolio/

About:

Hello, I am ready to design something! I love to learn from research, and craft meaningful decisions that blend into each product. I feel proud being able to bring solutions to people and see their smiles.

Highlights:

Software Skills: Figma, Adobe Suite, Sketch, Canva, Unity, HTML + CSS.

Design Skills: Design Thinking, User Research, Rapid Design, User Testing, Wireframing,

Interface Design, Interaction Design, Videography.

Soft Skills: Fast Learner, Task Management, Problem Solving, Critical Thinking.

Languages: English, Mandarin.

Experiences:

UX/UI Designer - AutoMetrics

September 2021 - March 2022

- Redesigned the user interface of a product that monitors welding operation quality,
 aimed to highlight the core features and provide users with brand new user-friendly
 and reliable monitor experience.
- Conducted user research and did competitive analysis to understand industry trends and current user pain points, which helped me to develop new goals and design directions before designing the monitor interface.
- Created marketing videos and brochures that highlighted the company's core features and main services. Also updated the company's website with new product design following company's brand guideline.

Graphic/UX Design Volunteer - Build a Biz Kids

February 2021 - April 2022

- Maintained the company brand style, designed multiple-day curricula for facilitators that are easy-to-follow, which then became the template for future courses.
- Worked with a company(YouMoveMe) to redesign their Franchise Opportunity Webpage.
- Worked with another designer to re-design the company founder's personal webpage which became more engaging and organised.
- Designed logo for the company's stock game for kids. Did Sketches, and iterations following company brand style while keeping kids as users in mind.

Education:

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Arts - Interactive Arts and Technology

Concentration in Design

September 2015 - December 2020